# Mohamed Sabry Mohamed Front End Developer | React/NextJs

• Alexandria, Egypt

≥ abosaadmohamed@gmail.com

+20 128 120 0365

## 22nd May 1993

**Egyptian** 

https://mohamed-sabry-portfolio.vercel.app/

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamedsabry3/

https://github.com/mohamedsabrie

## Summerry

I am a front-end web developer who enjoys coding and feels happiness while I do that.

I have 2 years of industry experience building websites and web apps.

I specialize in JavaScript and have professional experience working with React, Next, and Tailwind.css.

I also have experience working with TypeScript, Redux, and Recoil.

## **Education**

## **Bachelor of Electrical and Electronics Engineering**

2012 - 2018

**Al-Azhar University** 

Egypt

## **Professional Experience**

## **React Developer**

November 2021 – present

Soft IT

KSA, Remote

I work as Freelancer React developer for Soft IT on a long term real estate project in Saudi Arabia . I use Next.js, Tailwind.css and Recoil.js to handle the front end side of the web app

### **Front End Developer**

June 2021 – July 2022

AKOIN, Remote

USA, Remote

At Akoin, I work as a Front End Developer to develop the front end side of Crypto web apps

## **Projects in Production**

### MAD DAWGS

https://maddawgs-nft.vercel.app/ This is the MAD DAWGS web app. we use next.js, Talwind.css, Recoil, and ethers.js to handle the front-end side of the project

### Akoin-website

https://www.akoin.io/ This is the Akoin website. I was a collaborator working on the home & FAQs & Team pages. we have built it using next.js

### **Crypterns-website**

https://www.crypterns.com/ This is the crypterns website. I was a collaborator in this project . we have built it using next.js & Tailwind.css

## Skills

HTML/5 CSS/3

JavaScript TypeScript

React.js Redux

Recoil Next.js

Tailwind.css styled-components

Git Github

REST APIS Apollo GraphQL

Jira Agile, Scrum

Firebase Postman API

Material-UI Bootstrap

SASS, SCSS

## **Certificates**

• Web Development Professional Nanodegree from UDACITY ☑

# Languages

• Arabic • English